Welcome to mempool space, an open source project that provides data and tools to take your
ビットコイン経験をレベルアップするためにツールやデータを提供する オープンソースプロジェクトの
bitcoin experience to the next level.
mempool spaceにようこそ。
Our mempool dashboard provides an at-a-glance look at the realtime status of a bitcoin node’s mempool.
mempoolダッシュボードはリアルタイムに、特定ビットコイン ノードの一目で分かるメモリプール状態を表示します。
View bitcoin blocks through our one-of-a-kind visualization.
我々のユニークな可視化を用いて、ビットコインブロックを 閲覧できます。
Forecasted mempool blocks appear to the left of the white line, and confirmed blocks to the right.
予測されたメモリプールブロックは白線の 左に表示され、承認済みのブロックは右に表示されます。
Take a peek within a forecasted mempool block for a more granular view, including a visualization
より詳細な情報を見るのに、任意の予測されたメモリプール ブロックを閲覧できます。含まれるトランザクションの
of included transactions.
可視化も表示されます。
Drill down into the details at the transaction level.
トランザクションレベルの詳細まで掘り下げましょう。
And with real-time tracking, you can see the moment a transaction confirms!
リアルタイムの追跡で、トランザクションが 承認される瞬間を見えます。
If your transaction funds a new Lightning channel, you can see various details about
トランザクションが新しいライトニング チャンネルに資金を提供する場合、
it on our new Lightning network explorer.
新たな「ライトニングネットワークエキスプローラ」で様々な詳細を閲覧できます。
The mempool dashboard also includes a fee estimation widget that helps take the guesswork
mempoolダッシュボードに含まれる手数料の試算 ウィジェットのおかげで、当て推量に頼らずに
out of choosing an appropriate fee for your transactions.
トランザクションの手数料をより簡単に選択できます。
For miners, we’ve built a bitcoin mining dashboard that provides meaningful metrics
マイナーのために、手数料や補助金（subsidy） のデータ、ハッシュレートや難易度の統計値、
including fee and subsidy data, difficulty and hashrate stats, pool dominance, and more.
そしてプールのドミナンス（市場占有率）に関する有意義な データを提供する「マイニングダッシュボード」を開発しました。
Our historical graphs bring all of this data together and display it across time through
スタイリッシュな可視化を用いて、 歴史的なグラフはこのデータをまとめて
beautifully rendered visuals.
経時的な変更を表示します。
Mempool space doesn’t have any advertisements or third-party tracking.
Mempool spaceには広告やサードパーティーの トラッカーがありません。
Still, trusted third parties are security holes, and the most private way to look up
とはいえ、信頼すべき第三者はセキュリティーホールです。 だからこそ、自分のビットコインノードを利用して
your own addresses and transactions is through your own bitcoin node.
アドレスやトランザクションを閲覧するのが一番 プライベートな方法です。
We make this easy -- you can install your very own instance of mempool space with just
これをより簡単にするため、Umbrel、RaspiBlitz、Start9 EmbassyOS などのRasberry Piフルノードディストロで
1 click on raspberry pi full node distros like Umbrel, RaspiBlitz, Start9 EmbassyOS,
mempool spaceをワンクリックで インストールできるように開発しました。
and more -- or, for advanced users, install our pre-built docker images on your own server.
先進ユーザのために、事前構築済みDocker イメージをサーバーにもインストールできます。
Additionally, mempool space is integrated into a growing number of popular wallets and exchanges.
その上に、mempool spaceはますます多くの ウォレットや取引場に組み込まれています。
Explore the full Bitcoin ecosystem, with data from testnet, signet, liquid,
testnet、signet、リキッド、そしてライトニングネットワークのデータを全部含めて、
and now the lightning network.
ビットコインのエコシステムを完全に探検しましょう。
Tap into a powerful suite of tools that reveal useful information about the bitcoin network.
ビットコインネットワークに関する役立つ情報 を提供する一連のツールを利用しましょう。
Thanks to our generous individual and corporate sponsors, the Mempool space website and software
個人献金者と企業スポンサーの寛大な寄付のおかげで、 mempool spaceのウェブサイトもソフトウェアも
are freely available for anyone to use.
全ての人が自由に利用できます。
Mempool space itself is entirely self-hosted without any trusted third parties.
Mempool space自体は信頼される第三者を使わず、 完全にセルフホストされます。
Visit us at mempool dot space.
詳しくは「mempool ドット space」まで。